okay what is the trait what are the
traits and characteristics an individual
should possess to work on design
thinking hmm are we briefed on that one
I think that design thinking has been
one of those things that has been
somewhat oversold by consultants around
the world and and particularly it's been
sold as a new thing and if you look into
the history of it there's a book called
the universal traveller from 1971 that
that has all the graphics that I do and
the big design think tanks have have
popularized in the in the last 10 years
and it's not really anything new but but
in a wider sense to pay attention to how
we transform human intentionality and
how do we give expression to our
worldviews and how they inform our
intentions and our real and perceived
needs and then find solutions to them
that is what design is all about that
translation of worldview and intention
and real and perceived needs into ways
of meeting them and and we need to pay
much more attention to the upstream end
of the design process and and be be
mindful of whether we actually need the
things we we have in the design brief so
the first part of real Design Thinking
regenerative lis is to ask the question
is that actually needed and how would it
be designed in a way that it serves the
whole and how would that design be
informed by a place sourced knowledge by
the story of place the the bio cultural
uniqueness the both the cultural and the
uniqueness of the ecosystem and really
fit into this place and yeah I think
I'll leave it at that for for the this